[Music]
gnomes have a rule about food as long as
it doesn't harm anyone they can eat it
here are some things the Gnomes like to
eat all kinds of berries tree fruits
nuts mushrooms leaves honey and seeds
here's this
[Music]
poter it is about 103° out side right
now we are in a heat wave I think as
much of the country is unfortunately and
um little one was getting really really
uncomfortable so we have a tiny little
AC unit we plugged in so that he can be
um a little more comfortable at home and
not be so sweaty which was a little
alarming he was getting really
overheated poor guy we hoping
temperatures will cool down soon but I
wanted to just give you a little update
on how things are going um pregnancy
went very very well for the most part it
was not easy but everything that was
challenging was expected more or less
with fatigue the last couple weeks baby
was putting a lot of pressure on my
sciatic nerve and so I had shooting
pains and a lot of pain on one side of U
one of my legs and to the point that I
was bedridden for a little while um and
then then in quite moderate to severe
pain um at times and and that was that
was a little bit challenging end to the
pregnancy for sure I did feel quite
immobile the experience of giving birth
was uh very good um I will not share the
you know details of that here just
because it's not that important the
point is baby is here and he is healthy
yes it was certainly a quite painful
experience for sure
and um it took me quite a while to
recover I am still recovering physically
however I am feeling very healthy um
very very happy everything's so far been
going quite well there's nothing easy
about
parenting um it's so full of love but
it's challenging and it can be really
hard and stressful and overwhelming at
times for sure it's about how you
approach life challenges that can make
such a difference you know and and I
think here I've been reminding myself
that this little baby is teaching me so
much about mindfulness and patience and
being in the moment and I can be so
grateful for that even in the tough
moments when they're fussy or when
they're having a hard time settling in
some shape or form I am sending all of
you so much love I hope you're doing
well thank you for being here with me on
this journey whether or not this is a
life Journey you've decided to take or
we are living very different lives I
think it's so wonderful to share and
connect with each other
[Music]
is
I've been working on these pressed
flower art designs and a little bit of
my free time over the last few days I
certainly cut some Corners it's such an
aid climate over here that I found that
if I just put the flowers between glass
they actually dry just with within a day
because it is so dry right now it's
about 103 outside and there is just no
moisture so it's kind of funny doing it
this way it definitely wouldn't work
most of the time but right now it
happened to be and I wanted to cut some
Corners because I wanted to have these
ready for a little party later this week
doing this little project took a very
long time it took several days in little
Stolen Moments outside of parenting a
newborn and naturally I used to have
more time for hobbies for having a baby
thanks to the support of my partner and
my family helping me out making sure I
have a little bit time for myself now
and then I can remember that this very
temporary phase of parenting you know
when this baby is so young um and so
dependent on me um is a time that I'm
never going to get back I will have time
for these things again someday but I
will never get back that time I have
with my little one right now at this
phase of their life so it was a very
good reminder and I think something that
I would like to bring to all of you that
if you're ever in a time in your life
where you feel like you just don't have
the ability to put time into things or
to pursue certain dreams or Hobbies or
all you're doing is working or there's
other sort of lifestyle changes that
you've experienced that have just taken
you away from little things that you uh
may have enjoyed in the past perhaps it
will help to embrace the idea that you
know everything's Ever Changing
everything's temporary and what is
happening right now might be really
important it might be something you're
never going to get back and it is worth
those sacrifices and it's worth the
challenges you're experiencing right now
so I'm just really loving this stage
right now of just completely submersing
myself in Parenthood as well as taking
these little moments to do these things
I love so I hope that can just be
encouraging to all of you no matter what
life circumstances you are in right now
life is ever evolving ever changing and
even if you're in a slightly challenging
time right now it could be very
worthwhile once you look back on it or
it could be very meaningful if you
approach it in a new way I'm sending you
all so much love do check out my Etsy
shop if you're interested I only take a
small amount of orders these days
because I'm quite busy but I do have it
open and I also have some bonus content
on patreon you're always welcome to
check those things out there's no
obligation whatsoever but it helps keep
this channel going so I'm sending you so
much love thank you for being here and I
will see you again very soon goodbye
[Music]